

Daniel Hristov

Date of birth: 03/04/2002

Nationality: Bulgarian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

 Arno-Nitzsche-Strasse 42, null 04277 Leipzig - Marienbrunn, Germany

dan.hristov02@gmail.com

(+359) 884025891

(+49) 15151725107

Viber: +359884025891

Whatsapp Messenger: +4915

151725107

Whatsapp Messenger: +3598

84025891



ABOUT ME

I am 20 year old youth, currently a Physics undergraduate in Leipzig University in Germany. I have many years background which includes many different activities/assignments, both in person and from home office. I am looking for new and different projects, jobs and offers in order to get more experienced and advanced in my professional life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/03/2022 - CURRENT - Leipzig, Germany

Fahrgastzähler in MDV

Conoscope

15/04/2022 – CURRENT – Leipzig, Germany

Catering at Red Bull Arena

EMS

Having the responsibility to prepare the food (Such as wursts, fries, drinks, etc.) at the Leipzig's local stadium "Red Bull Arena". A great side job for a student, teaching me how to work in a fast pace and in a team with other people.

01/06/2021 - 30/07/2021 - Sofia

Programming teacher

MindHub Bulgaria

I was a programming teacher to kids between 5 and 9-year old, teaching them the basics of programming, game development and data structure, mainly used Skratch, Python and other child oriented software.

01/06/2019 - 01/09/2019 - Sofia, Bulgaria

Programmer(intern)

InterSoft Pro

During the summer break I was an intern in InterSoft Pro, where I learnt how to deal with the problems in a team work manner, how to deal with my own responsibilities and how to express my thoughts in code and make it work.

10/11/2019 – 09/12/2019 – Sofia, Bulgaria

Tour guide

FELS

I was a tour guide of different groups of exchange students in Bulgaria for one month. In that way I managed to gain experience and confidence as a guide, I made a lot of new friends and it was an opportunity for me to encounter new cultures.

01/01/2019 - 2021 - Sofia, Bulgaria

Translator

Self-empyed

I was translating texts from Spanish to Bulgarian and English and vice versa, online when somebody hired me. I was doing this freelance work as a way of side hustle and one more way to gain experience in communication with people and earning money.

01/09/2020 - 01/01/2022 - Sofia, Bulgaria

Web developer

Club of Nationalists of Bulgaria

Working in collaboration with Sofia University, I was the web administrator of their website for Nationalists (here). My main responsibilites were:

- Website maintenance (the act of regularly checking your website for issues and mistakes and keeping it updated and relevant)
- Content management
- Checking regularly the back-end(the server side) of the website

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2021 - CURRENT

Bachelor in Physics

Leipzig University

15/09/2016 - CURRENT - bul. Kniaz Aleksandar Dondukov 60, Sofia, Bulgaria

Student

First English Language School

14/05/2017 - 14/05/2019 - Sofia, district Sveta Troica, bl. 368, Sofia, Bulgaria

Tour Guide

Мишел M ET / Mishel M ET

C1 Level of proficiency of English language

IELTS

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Bulgarian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

| Listening C1 | Reading C1 | Spoken production C1 | Spoken interaction C1 | Writing C1 |
|------------------------|----------------------|--|---|----------------------|
| Spanish | | | | |
| Listening B1 | Reading B1 | Spoken production B1 | Spoken interaction B1 | Writing B1 |
| German | | | | |
| Listening A1 | Reading A1 | Spoken production A1 | Spoken interaction A1 | Writing A1 |

DIGITAL SKILLS

Digital Skills - Test Results

| Communication and collaboration | INTERMEDIATE Level 4 / 6 | õ |
|---------------------------------|--------------------------|---|
| Digital content creation | ADVANCED Level 6 / 6 | 5 |
| S Safety | ADVANCED Level 6 / 6 | 5 |
| Problem solving | ADVANCED Level 6 / 6 | 5 |

Results from <u>self-assessment</u> based on <u>The Digital Competence Framework 2.1</u>

My Digital Skills

Handling Information & Content

Microsoft PowerPoint / Microsoft Powerpoint / Microsoft Office / Microsoft Excel / Google Docs / So cial Media / Microsoft Servers / Zoom / Image Editing

Programming and programming languages

Web Design & Web Development / Content Management / Programming: C, C++, JAVA (J2EE) / Web Development: HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript / Unity 2D3D / Hosting and domains / Python / GIT & Github / Vercel / Android Development (Kotlin, Java)

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: AM
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

PROIECTS

15/09/2019 - 10/03/2020

"How You Doin'?"(HUD)

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Daniel.hud&hl=en&gl=US

This is my first Android application that I made. Its main purpose it to help people, who are not happy and want to improve their mood. With a given mood the app gives the user a list of different foods/movies and books, which are proven to make people happier.

10/08/2020 - 03/09/2020

The Twin Cars

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.SkardGames.TwoCarsClear&hl=en&gl=US

This is my most successful Android game so far! It is for two players using one device, each player controls one car, the goal is to work together and make a high score!

Jumpy Bird

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Daniel.FlapBird&hl=en&gl=US

My first Android game, made by idea of the original "Flappy Bird"

Medieval Jumpy Bird

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.Danick.MedievalJumpyBird&hl=en&gl=US

Better version of "lumpy Bird"

Stack Builder

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.DanielHristov.StackBuilder&hl=en&gl=US

Another arcade game made by me

Zigi Zagi

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.danick.zigizagi&hl=en&gl=US

The latest game I have done, it is again arcade, the purpose is to react quickly and avoid hitting in the walls.

HONOURS AND AWARDS

10/03/2019

Participant at the National Physics Olympiad - MON

I participated in the Physics Olympiad and managed to get to the third and hardest round of the Olympiad, which took place in Vurshec city. I was elected from my school, because I had the best results in Physics among all the students in my high school.

2012

First place at Chess competition for children between 10-16 year old. – Ministry of Sports Sofia

CREATIVE WORKS

CURRENT

Different portfolio templates

As a front-end programmer, I am selling online portfolio template websites. Here I will upload some of my works. For them, I used HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap.

Online Quiz on Bulgarian History

I made a quiz for Bulgarian history. This, I can say with confidence, is one of the best websites I have ever made! Unfortunately, it's no more online.